# HAMZA MUNAF

4 6th October 1997 @ hamzamunaf.11@gmail.com nttps://github.com/hamzamunaf

**\** +5419089529

♥ Corvallis, Oregon

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/hamza-munaf-048b56181/

# **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

Hard-working Computer Science major (3.5 GPA) currently attending Oregon State University, with 2+ years of work experience in IT support. Aiming to leverage a proven knowledge of  $programming\ skills, project\ planning, customer\ satisfaction\ skills\ and\ Usability\ testing\ skills\ for\ an$ internship as a developer.

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Student Technician, IS Client Services

#### **Oregon State University**

August 2018 - Ongoing

Corvallis, Oregon

- Sufficient knowledge about Banner, Splunk, Airwave, Microsoft Exchange Console, Active Directory and registering network devices
- Extensive support for Zoom which includes licensing and functionalities for customers.
- Supporting customer requests via walk-in, email or over the phone. The IS Service Desk supports over 100k customers, including students, staff, faculty, emeritus faculty, courtesy faculty, associates, and adjuncts.
- Responsibilities include installing operating systems and programs, troubleshooting hardware, and software issues and supporting applications like MS Office, Box, etc.
- Creating, maintaining, and entering information into Knowledge Base articles for documentation.

### Student Programmer/Analyst, Graduate School

#### **Oregon State University**

July 2020 - Ongoing

**♀** Corvallis, Oregon

- Supporting users with technical issues via email for Salesforce (User management and Application issues).
- Fixing bugs and writing testing scenarios for Salesforce applications.
- Working with GitHub repository and maintaining code coverage.
- Writing documentation on Salesforce applications.
- Testing applications with extensive cases and working with team to get them fixed.
- Techs: VSCode, Forcecode, Gitlens, Apex and etc

### **PROJECTS**

### Intro to Database

# **Oregon State University**

25Th September - 6Th December

♥ Corvallis, Oregon

- Setting up Database and building a website to retrieve entries from database as well as make changes to it
- GitHub Repo: https://github.com/hamzamunaf/CS340-Project
- Techs: MariaDB, MySQL, and Node.js

#### Software Engineering II

### **Oregon State University**

25Th September - 6Th December

♥ Corvallis, Oregon

- · Writing unit tests for an application in React and fixing some bugs.
- GitHub Repo: https://github.com/hamzamunaf/CS362-group-super11
- Techs: Enzyme, Mocha and Chai for testing React

#### Software Engineering I

### **Oregon State University**

25Th September - 6Th December

- ♥ Corvallis, Oregon
- Developing Aces up game in a team environment using Agile methodologies. Using Git version control to develop the whole game in to different branches.
- GitHub Repo: https://github.com/hamzamunaf/CS361-Sprint-4
- Techs: Apache Maven, Java, and Ninja Framework

#### Web Development

### **Oregon State University**

🛗 25Th September - 6Th December

Corvallis, Oregon

- Final Project for Web Development
- Making a website to show skills in using Handlebars, JavaScript, HTML, CSS and XMLHTTP request
- GitHub Repo: github.com/hamzamunaf/final-project-group-9-final-project-cs-290
- Techs: Node.js (Express, Handlebars and etc), JavaScript

### IT Support Chat Bot

### **Personal Project**

m December

- ♥ Corvallis, Oregon
- Support chat to troubleshoot computer's hardware and software issues and supporting two factor authentication app for Oregon State University
- Used an npm package and redirected them to Knowledge Base Article as per customer's query
- Package used: NodeJs and BotUI Github: https://github.com/hamzamunaf/servicedesk-botUI

### **EDUCATION**

B.Sc. Computer Science (Applied Security

#### **Oregon State University**

September 2017 - September 2021

# PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

**JavaScript** HTML

**CSS** 

C

Git C++

Python

Java

Git

### **STRENGTHS**

Development

C# JAVA JavaScript C++ NodeJS Maven

Related Classes

Object Orientated Programming Data Structures

Web Development

Bash | Powershell

Computer Architecture Assembly Language

Computer Networks | Statistics for Engineers

Fundamentals of Software Engineering I

**Operating Systems** 

Fundamentals of Software Engineering II

Introduction to Database Analysis of Algorithm

Development Tools – IDE

Visual Studio | IntelliJ | Atom

### LANGUAGES

**English** Urdu Hindi



# HONOR/AWARDS

- International Provost Scholarship
- Dean's Honor List (Fall 2019)
- Dean's Honor List (Spring 2020)